SAYUMI NAKAMURA

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

Energetic front-end web developer, seeking to use my passion for building and designing websites. Ambitious, flexible team member who enjoys learning new skills and up-to-date technologies, adept at maintaining cordial and professional relationships with colleagues and customers. Strong problem solving and analytical skill with 3+ years of supply chain experience.

SKILLS

- -HTML5 / CSS3
- -JavaScript
- -React.js / Redux
- -GitHub
- -Figma
- -BootStrap
- -Sass
- -iQuery
- -Microsoft Excel, PowerPoint, Word
- -Workflow optimization
- -Knowledge of logistics, supply chain management and transportation
- -Supply planning
- -IELTS Overall 6.5

CONTACT

Cell: +81-80-3539-7069 sayumi.nkmr.2019@gmail.com Vancouver, B.C. https://www.linkedin.com/in/sayumi-n https://github.com/Sayumi-n https://sayuminakamura.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

Website Developer and Sales Associate
Noella Trading Company Limited.| Sept 2019 - Mar 2020

Vancouver, B.C.

- Created store website using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and jQuery, building a digital-first culture
- Fostered an atmosphere of hospitality and flexibility with guests
- Organized and changed displays regularly with a consideration of buying audience and season

Supply Planning and Logistics

Tokyo, Japan

Graphic Packaging International, LLC. | Dec 2015 - Aug 2019

- Reviewed operational efficiency with team members to renew the ERP system
- Controlled inventory levels and delivery of sheeted paperboard with outsourcing warehouses across Japan, handled 6,000MT annually
- Provided in-depth category and item level analysis
- Ensured traceability for client to implement FSC (Forest Stewardship Council) certified products
- Successfully met clients' demand while sales has been increased by 34% and achieved result of 15% dead stock reduction in 2017 (Received a 2017 President Leadership Award)
- Troubleshooting customer claims, researched and analyzed material complaints, monitoring progress until resolution provided

Project Coordinator

Tokyo, Japan

Triangle Innovator Program | Jun 2018 - Jan 2019

- Internship at a social venture with working professionals from different companies, learned social leadership and how to develop new businesses using Lean Startup methods
- Set up objectives and presented solution for a 15-year-old NPO Green Bird

EDUCATION

Diploma: Web and Mobile App Development

Vancouver, B.C.

Cornerstone International Community College of Canada \mid Aug 2019 - Current Specialization in Web Development

Courses include:

- -Introduction to Computing / Algorithms, Flow Charts and Problem Solving
- -Java (Introduction to Object Oriented Programming) / HTML5 / CSS3 / JavaScript
- -React.js and Modern Javascript / Node.js Fundamentals

Bachelor of Arts: International Law And Business

Tokyo, Japan

Chuo University | Apr 2011 - Mar 2015

Activity: Design Society

PROJECTS

React.js Web App Fridge Haiku | Apr 2020

Company Website
Noella Trading Company Ltd. | Mar 2020